A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Office of the Secretary of Public Safety, 2000-2006 (bulk 2002-2005)
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of the Virginia Office of the Secretary of Public Safety, 2000-2006 (bulk 2002-2005)
The Library of Virginia
42405
34.3 cu. ft. (101 boxes)
Virginia Office of the Secretary of Public Safety
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Privacy protected and confidential information is restricted from public access for 75 years per Code of Virginia 42.1-78. When possible, privacy-protected information has been redacted. If redaction was not an option, the entire document was sealed, but not removed from the collection. Sealed information may include, but is not limited to: attorney-client privileged documents, medical information, social security numbers, proprietary information, Department of Corrections inmate classification material, and Parole Board review documents. Attorney-client privileged documents are closed indefinitely.
Acquisition Information
Transferred by Iva B. Frizzell, Office of the Secretary of Public Safety, 1111 E. Broad Street, Richmond, Virginia 23219, 12 January 2006.
Biographical/Historical Information
In 1970, the Governor's Management Commission Study recommended the creation of six "Deputy Governors" to assist the Chief Executive in his managerial duties. Compatible functions of government were grouped under these administrative heads, who would serve as the Governor's top management team.
The office of the Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety was created on April 8, 1972. Originally, the Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety oversaw the State Highway Commission, Division of Motor Vehicles, Department of State Police, Highway Safety Division, Office of Emergency Services, Department of Military Affairs, Virginia State Crime Commission, and the Law Enforcement Officers Training Standards Commission. Since that time, the Office has undergone a series of administrative reorganizations. On April 12, 1976, the Legislature established separate secretariats for transportation and public safety, effective July 1, 1976. On July 1, 1984, the offices were again combined. Finally, the two became separate offices on February 22, 1990, and have remained separate in the years since.
The Secretary of Public Safety is a member of the Governor's Cabinet, is appointed by the governor, and is subject to confirmation by the General Assembly. Throughout Governor Mark R. Warner's term (2002-2006), the Secretary of Public Safety was responsible for the direction of, or had jurisdiction over, 11 state agencies and boards. The agencies and boards under the heading of the Secretary of Public Safety during the Warner administration are as follows: Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, Commonwealth's Attorneys' Services Council, Department of Correctional Education, Department of Corrections, Department of Criminal Justice Services, Department of Emergency Management, Department of Fire Programs, Department of Juvenile Justice, Department of Military Affairs, the Virginia Parole Board, and the Virginia State Police.
On December 20, 2001, Governor Mark R. Warner appointed John W. Marshall as his Secretary of Public Safety. Prior to taking this position, Marshall had served as a trooper, special agent, training academy instructor, and sergeant with the Virginia State Police. In 1994, President William J. Clinton appointed Marshall to serve as the United States Marshal for the Eastern District of Virginia. In 1999, he was nominated to serve as director of the United States Marshals Service. He was the first African-American to hold this position.
On December 29, 2001, Governor Warner appointed Robert P. Crouch, Jr. as Chief Deputy Secretary of Public Safety. Later, in March 2002, Barry R. Green was appointed to serve as Deputy Secretary, and Marilyn P. Harris was appointed to serve as Assistant Secretary of Public Safety, as well as the Director of the Governor's Office for Substance Abuse Prevention (GOSAP). In April 2002, Dawn Smith was also asked to serve as an Assistant Secretary, a position she held throughout the four-year term. Crouch left in May 2005 to become Counselor to the Governor, and Green left in June 2005 to take over as Director of the Department of Juvenile Justice. Harris was then appointed as Deputy Secretary, and served in that position until the end of Governor Warner's term.
Information about this office is also available in the archived website files of the Office of the Secretary of Public Safety, (2005-2006). They can be found by searching the Library of Virginia's catalog using "Secretary of Public Safety" as the subject.
Scope and Content
Constituent and internal correspondence, decision briefs, legislative files, speeches, and other working papers and records created and collected by the Office of the Secretary of Public Safety during the gubernatorial term of Virginia Governor Mark R. Warner, 2002-2006. This collection consists of 11 records series which document the activities of the Office of the Secretary of Public Safety, as well as the agencies and boards which fall under its heading.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Agency Correspondence, 2002-2005
Series II. Appointment Calendars, 2002-2006
Series III. Constituent Correspondence, 2002-2006
Series IV. Decision Briefs, 2002-2005
Series V. Federal Grants, 2002-2005
Series VI. Historical Records, 2002-2005
Series VII. Legislative Files, 2001-2005
Series VIII. Public Relations Files, 2001-2005
Series IX. Secretary's Correspondence, 2002-2006
Series X. Special Projects and Programs, 2000-2005
Series XI. Speeches, 2002-2005
Contents List
- Series I. Agency Correspondence, 2002-2005., Extent: 2.1 cu. ft. (Box 1-6)
  This series contains files composed of correspondence (constituent and internal), along with supporting material such as reports, proposals, and other working papers. Several state agencies and boards operated under the Office of the Secretary of Public Safety during the Warner Administration. They are as follows: the Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, the Commonwealth's Attorneys' Services Council, the Department of Correctional Education, the Department of Corrections, the Department of Criminal Justice Services, the Department of Emergency Management, the Department of Fire Programs, the Department of Forensic Science, the Department of Juvenile Justice, the Department of Military Affairs, the Parole Board, and the Virginia State Police.
  The correspondence files contain mostly correspondence between the agencies and the Office of the Secretary of Public Safety regarding issues affecting that particular department or board. References to budgetary matters, status reports, assessments, mandates, and requests for approval of reports, speeches and appearances are frequently found in this material. These files also provide supporting documentation and background information on many topics. Researchers interested in a particular issue should also utilize the Historical Records series because it contains correspondence as well.
  The files are arranged alphabetically by the name of the department or board, then chronologically within.
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, 2002 March-August. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, 2002 September-December. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, 2003. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, 2004. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, 2005. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Commonwealth's Attorneys' Services Council, 2002-2005. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correctional Education, Dept. of, 2002-2005. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Corrections, Dept. of, 2002-2003 July. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Corrections, Dept. of, 2003 August-September. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Corrections, Dept. of, 2003 October-December. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Corrections, Dept. of, 2004 January. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Corrections, Dept. of, 2004 February-June. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Corrections, Dept. of, 2004 July. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Corrections, Dept. of, 2004 August-November. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Corrections, Dept. of, 2004 December-2005 April. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Corrections, Dept. of, 2005 May-June. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Corrections, Dept. of, 2005 July-September. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Corrections, Dept. of, 2005 October-December. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Criminal Justice Services, Dept. of, 2002. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Criminal Justice Services, Dept. of, 2002 February-June. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Criminal Justice Services, Dept. of, 2002 July-December. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Criminal Justice Services, Dept. of, 2003 January-July. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Criminal Justice Services, Dept. of, 2003 August-December. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Criminal Justice Services, Dept. of, 2004 January-September. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Criminal Justice Services, Dept. of, 2004 September-December. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Criminal Justice Services, Dept. of, 2005 January-August. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Criminal Justice Services, Dept. of, 2005 September-November. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Emergency Management, Dept. of, 2002 February-July. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Emergency Management, Dept. of, 2002 September-2003 September. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Emergency Management, Dept. of, 2004 October-December. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Emergency Management, Dept. of, 2005 January-May. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Emergency Management, Dept. of, 2005 June-July. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Emergency Management, Dept. of, 2005 July-August. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Emergency Management, Dept. of, 2005 October-December. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Fire Programs, Dept. of, 2002. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Fire Programs, Dept. of, 2003 January-September. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Fire Programs, Dept. of, 2003 October-2005. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Forensic Science, Dept. of, 2005. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Juvenile Justice, Dept. of, 2002. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Juvenile Justice, Dept. of, 2003. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Juvenile Justice, Dept. of, 2004 January-September. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Juvenile Justice, Dept. of, 2004 October-November. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Juvenile Justice, Dept. of, 2005 January. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Juvenile Justice, Dept. of, 2005 February-October. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Military Affairs, Dept. of, 2002 February-2003 July. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Military Affairs, Dept. of, 2003 October-2005. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Parole Board, 2002-2005. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - State Police, 2002 January-July. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - State Police, 2002 August-December. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - State Police, 2003 January-May. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - State Police, 2003 June-July. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - State Police, 2003 August-September. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - State Police, 2003 October-December. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - State Police, 2004 January-May. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - State Police, 2004 June-August. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - State Police, 2004 September. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - State Police, 2004 October-December. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - State Police, 2005 January-March. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - State Police, 2005 April-May. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - State Police, 2005 June. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - State Police, 2005 July. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - State Police, 2005 August. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - State Police, 2005 September-December. (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Series II. Appointment Calendars, 2002-2006., Extent: 1 folder. (Box 6)
  Contains the monthly appointment calendars of John W. Marshall, Secretary of Public Safety.
  Arranged chronologically by month.
  - Appointment Calendars (John W. Marshall), 2002-2006. (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Series III. Constituent Correspondence, 2002-2006., Extent: 10.7 cu. ft. (Box 7-37)
  Contains constituent correspondence pertaining to all agencies and boards overseen by the Office of the Secretary of Public Safety. Most of the letters were originally addressed to Governor Warner, but were assigned to the Secretary of Public Safety for response based on their subject matter. A large number of letters pertain to prisoners held by the Department of Corrections. In many cases family members wrote to the Governor for assistance in obtaining pardons, granting parole, and conducting investigations. Other topics included in the correspondence include gun control legislation, budget shortfalls in terms of the Pre-Release and Post-Incarceration Services (PAPIS), Substance Abuse Reduction Effort (SABRE), and drug court programs. Additional subjects include the implementation of a Virginia Amber Alert system, the D.C. sniper situation, Alcoholic Beverage Control (ABC) issues, the Roger Coleman DNA case, the "no parole" law, and hurricane/disaster relief. Correspondence from 2002 makes up a little more than half of the material. This series contains restricted information that has either been redacted or sealed. The material may include, but is not limited to, medical records, social security numbers, Department of Corrections inmate classification material, and Parole Board review documents.
  The files are arranged by the system number generated by the Governor's Office, which puts the letters in very rough chronological order. Researchers interested in a particular topic or agency should also utilize the Agency Correspondence and Historical Records series because they contain correspondence, as well as supporting documentation.
  - #2000104 - 2000137, 2002. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - #2000138 - 2000145, 2002. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - #2000148 - 2000188, 2002. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - #2000189 - 2000242, 2002. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - #2000243 - 2000263, 2002. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - #2000495 - 2000512, 2002. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - #2000536 - 2000724, 2002. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - #2000773 - 2001994, 2002. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - #2002092 - 2002474, 2002. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - #2002477 - 2002839, 2002. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - #2002842 - 2002901, 2002. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - #2002967 - 2003356, 2002. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - #2003502 - 2003775, 2002. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - #2003781 - 2004007, 2002. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - #2004032 - 2004118, 2002. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - #2004119 - 2004356, 2002. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - #2004357 - 2004660, 2002. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - #2004665 - 2004895, 2002. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - #2004931 - 2005344, 2002. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - #2005428 - 2005624, 2002. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - #2005712 - 2005852, 2002. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - #2005881 - 2005918, 2002. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - #2005919 - 2006035, 2002. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - #2006036 - 2006216, 2002. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - #2006217 - 2006400, 2002. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - #2006402 - 2006727, 2002. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - #2006728 - 2007327, 2002. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - #2007333 - 2007707, 2002. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - #2007750 - 2007824, 2002. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - #2007848 - 2008117, 2002. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - #2008128 - 2008483, 2002. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - #2008623 - 2009884, 2002. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - #2009890 - 2010356, 2002. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - #2010358 - 2010404, 2002. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - #2010405 - 2010444, 2002. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - #2010445 - 2010476, 2002. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - #2010478 - 2010556, 2002. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - #2010571 - 2010835, 2002. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - #2010853 - 2010856, 2002. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - #2010886 - 2010988, 2002. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - #2011032 - 2011180, 2002. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - #2011199 - 2011361, 2002. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - #2011367 - 2011585, 2002. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - #2011573 - 2011616, 2002. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - #2011617 - 2011688, 2002. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - #2011690 - 2011815, 2002. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - #2011816 - 2012023, 2002. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - #2012047 - 2012144, 2002. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - #2012145 - 2012327, 2002. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - #2012328 - 2012396, 2002. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - #2012397 - 2012408, 2002. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - #2012410 - 2012634, 2002. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - #2012639 - 2012709, 2002. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - #2012710 - 2012904, 2002. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - #2012906 - 2013059, 2002. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - #2013061 - 2013179, 2002. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - #2013181 - 2013248, 2002. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - #2013249, 2002. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - #2013261 - 2013389, 2002. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - #2013390 - 2013527, 2002. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - #2013528 - 2013916, 2002. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - #2013918 - 2014045, 2002. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - #2014066, 2002. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - #2014078 - 2014482, 2002. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - #2014483 - 2014753, 2002. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - #2014755 - 2015227, 2002. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - #2015318 - 2015424, 2002. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - #2015425 - 2015756, 2002. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - #2015796 - 2016021, 2002. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - #2016022 - 2016618, 2002. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - #2016670 - 2016880, 2002. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - #2016894 - 2017653, 2002. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - #2017654 - 2018419, 2002. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - #2018500 - 2019013, 2002. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - #2019022 - 2019841, 2002. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - #2019842 - 2020095, 2002. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - #2020107 - 2020606, 2002. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - #2020608 - 2021007, 2002. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - #2021033 - 2021415, 2002. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - #2021748 - 2022339, 2002. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - #2022345 - 2023223, 2002. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - #2023224 - 2023676, 2002. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - #2023681 - 2023954, 2002. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - #2023955 - 2024097, 2002. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - #2024121 - 2025122, 2002. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - #2025123 - 2026117, 2002. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - #2026119 - 2026663, 2002. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - #2026664 - 2027056, 2002. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - #2027088 - 2027586, 2002. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - #2027596 - 2027773, 2002. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - #2027773, 2002. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - #2027785 - 2030010, 2002. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - #2030105 - 2030716, 2002. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - #2030722 - 2031115, 2002. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - #2031164 - 2031779, 2002. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - #2031798 - 2032221, 2002. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - #2032223 - 2032716, 2002. (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - #2032717 - 2033000, 2002. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - #2033024 - 2033432, 2002. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - #2033440 - 2033746, 2002. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - #2033747 - 2034097, 2002. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - #2034138 - 2034639, 2002. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - #2034650 - 2034931, 2002. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - #2035013 - 2035293, 2002. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - #2035297 - 2035485, 2002. (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - #2035496 - 2035736, 2002. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - #2035749 - 2035994, 2002. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - #2036019 - 2036277, 2002. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - #2036294 - 2036469, 2002. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - #2036574 - 2036821, 2002. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - #2036823 - 2037053, 2002. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - #2037070 - 2037609, 2002. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - #2037649 - 2038039, 2002. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - #2038047 - 2037465, 2002. (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - #2038368 - 2038481, 2002. (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - #2038501 - 2038685, 2002. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - #2038686 - 2038970, 2002. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - #2038990 - 2039328, 2002. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - #2039334 - 2039461, 2002. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - #2039678 - 2039971, 2002. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - #2039977 - 2040276, 2002. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - #2040278 - 2040488, 2002. (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - #2040493 - 2041242, 2002. (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - #2041378 - 2041874, 2002. (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - #2042063 - 2042371, 2002. (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - #2042372 - 2042720, 2002. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - #2042724 - 2043228, 2002. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - #2043233 - 2043247, 2002. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - #2043248 - 2043735, 2002. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - #2043740 - 2044212, 2002. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - #2044213 - 2045229, 2002. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - #2045230 - 2045648, 2002. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - #2045649 - 2047695, 2002. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - #2047913 - 2049291, 2002. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - #2049384 - 2049800, 2002. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - #2049801 - 2050217, 2002. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - #2052450 - 2050653, 2002. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - #2050654 - 2052485, 2002. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - #2052659 - 2052868, 2002. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - #2052862 - 2053214, 2002. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - #2053215 - 2054009, 2002. (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - #2054077 - 2054577, 2002. (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - #2054578 - 2054793, 2002. (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - #2054802 - 2054999, 2002. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - #2055001 - 2055029, 2002. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - #2055031 - 2055258, 2002. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - #2055259 - 2055313, 2002. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - #2055320 - 2055695, 2002. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - #2055741 - 2056335, 2002. (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - #2056343 - 2056532, 2002. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - #2056553 - 2056677, 2002. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - #2056679 - 2056989, 2002. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - #2056990 - 2057072, 2002. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - #2057181 - 2057343, 2002. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - #2058162 - 2058206, 2002. (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - #2058227 - 2059935, 2002. (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - #2057333 - 2057968, 2002. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - #2060049 - 2065267, 2002. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - #2065316 - 2068920, 2002-2003. (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - #2068922 - 2073838, 2002-2003. (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - #2074157 - 2080839, 2003. (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - #2081052 - 2087072, 2003. (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - #2087133 - 2093360, 2003. (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - #2093379 - 2100683, 2003. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - #2100722, 2003. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - #2100722, 2003. (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - #2100722, 2003. (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - #2100940 - 2110690, 2003. (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - #2110706 - 2117105, 2003. (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - #2117160 - 2123724, 2003. (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - #2123870 - 2130463, 2003. (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - #2130831 - 2134458, 2003. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - #2134459 - 2136854, 2003. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - #2137166 - 2141510, 2003. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - #2141998 - 2146493, 2003. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - #2146502 - 2150148, 2003. (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - #2150152 - 2157800, 2003. (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - #2157849 - 2159601, 2003. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - #2159699 - 2165837, 2003. (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - #2166568 - 2171694, 2003. (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - #2172271 - 2175538, 2003. (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - #2177132 - 2179828, 2003. (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - #2180686 - 2184961, 2003. (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - #2184965 - 2189307, 2003. (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - #2189325 - 2192772, 2003. (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - #2194058 - 2197257, 2003. (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - #2197271 - 2198753, 2003. (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - #2199449 - 2202094, 2003. (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - #2202267 - 2205819, 2003. (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - #2205846 - 2209488, 2003. (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - #2209500 - 2210323, 2003. (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - #2210341 - 2214703, 2003. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - #2215122 - 2217078, 2003. (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - #2217328 - 2218435, 2003. (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - #2218548 - 2222084, 2003. (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - #2222182 - 2225265, 2003. (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - #2226210 - 2228756, 2003. (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - #2228770 - 2233390, 2003. (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - #2234382 - 2238578, 2003. (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - #2238737 - 2243442, 2003-2004. (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - #2244264 - 2247318, 2004. (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - #2247339 - 2249464, 2004. (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - #2250002 - 2255529, 2004. (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - #2255547 - 2258318, 2004. (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - #2258749 - 2261430, 2004. (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - #2261906 - 2265125, 2004. (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - #2265385 - 2268470, 2004. (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - #2268489 - 2266569, 2004. (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - #2268937 - 2274691, 2004. (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - #2275577 - 2282320, 2004. (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - #2282355 - 2284160, 2004. (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - #2284491 - 2288739, 2004. (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - #2289979 - 2296131, 2004. (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - #2296229 - 2300139, 2004. (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - #2300757 - 2308694, 2004. (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - #2309070 - 2309386, 2004. (Box 31, Folder 1)